https://www.sysmex.nl/n/nl-en/legal/legal-information.html

Company
Who is Sysmex ?
Who is Sysmex ?
Back
Who is Sysmex ?
Company
Who is Sysmex ?
Legal information
We believe that you should always know what data Sysmex collects about you and how we process these. We are updating our privacy policy in light of the new data protection law (GDPR) and our desire for transparency, to enable to you make the best decision at all times about the data you share with us.This privacy statement concerns the personal customer data collected by Sysmex Nederland B.V. and Sysmex Belgium N.V. with their registered office in:Sysmex Nederland B.V. 			Ecustraat 11 			4879 NP Etten-Leur 			The NetherlandsSysmex Belgium N.V 			Park Rozendal, Building A 			Terhulpsesteenweg 6a 			1560 Hoeilaart, Belgium Personal data we process Sysmex Nederland B.V. & Sysmex Belgium N.V. process your personal data because you use our services and/or because you provide the data to us yourself. The following is an overview of the personal data we process: Personal detailsAcademic title, position, functionFirst and last nameAddress details of the organisationTelephone number of the organisation or departmentE-mail address Online data: See Online privacy statementSpecial and/or sensitive personal data we process
Sysmex Nederland B.V. & Sysmex Belgium N.V. do not process special and/or sensitive personal information, such as race, ethnic background, political preferences, religion, health, sexuality, etc.The purpose for which and the basis on which we process personal data Sysmex Nederland B.V. & Sysmex Belgium N.V. process your personal data for the following purposes:To process paymentsTo send out our newsletter and/or promotional materialsTo call or e-mail you if this is necessary for us to provide our servicesTo inform you about changes in our services or productsTo offer you the opportunity to create an account via MySysmex and Sysmex Academy OnlineTo deliver goods and services to youSysmex Nederland B.V. & Sysmex Belgium N.V. analyse your behaviour, not your personal data, on the website in order to improve the website and to offer products and services in line with your preferences.Sysmex Nederland B.V. & Sysmex Belgium N.V. also process personal data if we are required to do so by law, such as data we need to file our taxes, for example.How long we retain personal data Sysmex Nederland B.V. & Sysmex Belgium N.V. do not keep your personal data any longer than is strictly necessary for the purposes for which your data are collected. We use the statutory retention periods or regulations.Sharing of personal data with third parties Sysmex Nederland B.V. & Sysmex Belgium N.V. share data with third parties only if this is necessary for the implementation of our agreement with you or to comply with a legal requirement. Cookies or similar techniques we use à Online privacy statementSysmex Nederland B.V. & Sysmex Belgium N.V. use functional, analytical and tracking cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored in the browser of your computer, tablet or smartphone the first time you visit this website. Sysmex Nederland B.V. & Sysmex Belgium N.V. use cookies with a purely technical functionality. These make sure that the website works properly and that your preference settings are remembered, for example. These cookies are also used to make sure the website runs smoothly and for website optimisation. We also use cookies to keep track of your browsing behaviour so we can offer customised content and advertisements. We already informed you about these cookies and asked your permission to use them when you visited our website the first time. You can decline cookies by changing the setting of your internet browser so it does not store cookies. You can also delete all previously stored information via your browser settings. We also use the tool HubSpot. See https://legal.hubspot.com/privacy-policy for a detailed explanation of our analytical tool HubSpot. We also use LinkedIn. Check https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy?_l=nl_NL for the privacy statement of LinkedIn. Inspecting, changing or erasing data You have the right to inspect, rectify or erase your data. You also have the right to withdraw your consent for the data processing or to object to the processing of your personal data by Sysmex Nederland B.V. & Sysmex Belgium N.V. and you have the right to data portability. This means that you can submit a request to us to send the personal data we have concerning you in a computer file to you or to another organisation specified by you.  Please send requests to inspect, rectify, erase or transfer your personal data or requests to withdraw your consent or objection to the processing of your personal data toprivacy@sysmex.nl . We will respond to your request as soon as possible, but in any case within four weeks. Sysmex Nederland B.V. & Sysmex Belgium N.V. would also like to point out that you have the option of filing a complaint with the national supervisory authority, the Dutch Data Protection Authority. You can do this via the following link: https://autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl/nl/contact-met-de-autoriteit-persoonsgegevens/tip-ons How we keep personal data secure Sysmex Nederland B.V. & Sysmex Belgium N.V. take the protection of your data seriously and they take appropriate measures to prevent abuse, loss, unauthorised access, unwanted publication and unauthorised changes. Nevertheless, if you think that your data are not secure or that there are signs of abuse, please contact our customer service or e-mail us at: privacy@sysmex.nl .Kind regards,Sysmex
Sysmex Belgium N.V.
Terhulpsesteenweg 6a, Building A
1560 Hoeilaart
Belgium
+32 (0)2 7697474
+32 (0)2 7697499
info@sysmex.be
Sysmex Nederland B.V.
P.O. Box 251
4870 AG Etten-Leur
The Netherlands
+31 (0)76 5086000
+31 (0)76 5086086
info@sysmex.nl
Service
Sitemap
Social Media
Imprint
Legal information
Imprint
Legal information
Copyright © Sysmex Europe GmbH. All rights reserved.
Customize your experience
We use cookies to enable you to optimally use our Website and to improve our communication with you. We shall take your selection into account and use only the data for which you give us your consent.
Accept all cookies
Enable cookies only for statistical purposes
Accept only essential cookies *
* May lead to restrictions in content and in the user experience
Data privacy
Legal informational Page
Detail
Detail about cookies
Essential cookies
These cookies help to make our website usable by enabling basic features such as page navigation and access to secure areas of our website. Our website cannot function properly without these cookies.
Statistics cookies
By collecting information anonymously, these cookies help us to understand how visitors interact with our website. This information enables us to continually improve our platform.
Marketing cookies
are used to track visitors on websites. The intention is to show advertisements that are relevant and appealing to the individual user and are, therefore, valuable to publishers and third-party advertisers.
An overview of all cookies can be found here
Hide
